Finding Aid for the S.A. Griffin collection of underground poetry, Scott Wannberg, and The Carma Bums LSC.2248
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Performance files (Box 114, Box 179, Box 180, Box 181, Box 182, Box 183, Box 184, Box 185, Box 186, Box 187, Box 188, Box 189, Box 190, Box 191, Box 192, Box 194, Box 195, Box 196, Box 197, Box 198, Box 199, Box 200, Box 201, Box 202, Box 203, Box 204, Box 205, Box 206, Box 207, Box 208, Box 209, 
  - Audiovisual materials (Box 195, Box 196, Box 197, Box 198, Box 199, Box 200, Box 201, Box 202, Box 203, Box 204, Box 205, Box 206, Box 207, Box 208, Box 209, Box 210, Box 330, Box 331)
    Box 199: Jack Micheline, Williams Carlos Williams/Saccharine Trust, Sebastin Cabot and Other Stuff / William Burroughs, Jack Kerouac on Beat Generation, Mike Bruner 1984, Jack Micheline MVD Boulder, Blakeslee Stevens American Hotel/Humanesque, Fred Neil Live, Scott Wannberg, Jack Brewer, Diane DiPrima Interview with Marie Kazalia, Stuart Z Perkoff / James Ryan Morris, Mike Meloan, Bob Branaman, Lon Spiegelman Mail Art Interview, Scott Wannberg 10/1994, Scott Wannberg 1991, Scott Wannberg #3, Scott Wannberg 07/24/1996, Scott Wannberg 06/24/1991, Mike Mollett Mudpeople Interview, and Neal Cassady.
    Box 200: VHS tapes include Bukowski at Bellevue, Sheree's Reflections on Bob Flanagan, and The Best Hotel on Skid Row.
    Box 201: The bulk of these video tapes document The Carma Bums.
    Box 202: These video tapes document the Boss Poetry series that Griffin produced at EZTV.
    Box 203: Tapes include Open Ended It at the Onyx / Echo, The Ringling Sisters Benefit, Cabaret X, and onTarget Live at The Grassy Knoll.
    Box 204: Materials include Beat Scene recordings of Charles Bukowski reading and a President K "In Acapulco" 45 rpm record allegedly obtained from an F.B.I. file and gifted to Griffin by Looseleaf.
    Box 205: The bulk of the CDs are marko x recordings. Audio cassette tapes include S.A. Griffin with Jack Brewer "Believe in the Love" and Tracy & the Hindenburg Ground Crew "Margaret Dumont."
    Box 206: DVDs include Venice West and the LA Scene, A History Lesson Part I: Punk Rock in Los Angeles in 1984, Poetic Hoohaw, If I Scratch, If I Write, and Meeting Mr. Mumps. This box also contains "The Bust" Tracy & the Hindenburg Ground Crew music video in which Griffin performs the role of Chief Whitman.
    Box 207: Tapes include Rhino Records' Hollyword, Charles Bukowski's Run With The Hunted, and the Cassette Gazette Special: Charles Bukowski recorded by Nola Express, 1970.
    Box 208: DVDs include Mary Kerr's Temple Ghosts, Goldmouth and other films by Robert Branaman. CDs include the Scott Wannberg Memorial at Beyond Baroque, Todd Moore readings, The Carma Bums No Seat Belts Tour of Words 1989 at the Living Batch, James Ryan Morris with Larry Lake Denver Poets Day 1978, The Kid in America Tony Scibella Live at Cafe Nepenthe 1979, John Thomas Our Life, F.N. Wright The Homerecordings, Poetry by Frank T. Rios, Rodeo for the Sheepish Ellyn Maybe, 13 Poems Stuart Z. Perkoff, Black Angeles with Wanda Coleman and Michelle T. Clinton, and High Priestess of Word by Wanda Coleman.
    Box 209: Tapes include Another Fucking Hippie w/ Ken Tao's Alchemical Orchestra, Black Girl, Fuzzy Doodah, S.A. Griffin on KXLU, and Laurel Ann Bogen in Vulnerable Street.
    Box 210: Tapes include Tales of Ordinary Madness, Jim Rose Circus Side Show, and the EZTV videocassette Polly Perverse Strikes Again! with S.A. Griffin.
    Box 330: VHS tapes include Tumbleweed in a Box in three parts, onTarget Live at THE GRASSY KNOLL tape 1, John Dullaghan Reels Tape #4, Further, Further On, and KEY-Z Productions Still Kesey! and The Merry Pranksters Part One. Includes a DVD of the UK and Hackford Bukwoski documentaries.
    Box 331: VHS tapes include Peace March Night Lhasa; Micheline Memorial; Bukowski by Taylor Hackford; Mudpeople; Jack Micheline Reads; Swinging in the Shadows Venice West and the LA Scene; Tumbleweed in a Box; Night of the Living Sidemen by Doug Knott; L. Aliens, The Looseleaf Binder Report...; Approaching Omega; untitled performance footage; Ed and Marcia Ward's Robber Sly...; Tony Goodstone Poetry in Performance; Smokin' the Chronic in Amsterdam; S.A. Griffin - "Ban This Art;" The Looseleaf Report; Bygone Dayz by Bob Branaman; Wig Rodeo by Marcel de Jure; Cowboy Poets by Kim Shelton; Possum Dixon "Radio Comet;" Bookmark The Ordinary Madness of Charles Bukowski; Venice West and the LA Scene Demo; Psychic Defuse Train for Ex-Lovers; Poetry Slipped on a Banana; Robert Greenfield Show...; The Charles Bukowski Tapes Master; Heaven is One Long Naked...; Greenfield Code...; and The Carma Bums 1990. Cassettes include Onword Radio promos, Background music, Hotel Bums Bookstore Open, Hal (Bus Repair), Graveyard Sante Fe, Meeting Pixel, If I had the Money..., Hotel, Head Bolts Cards, Penny Lane, Psychic Reading for S.A., Eldridge Cleaver, and Bus movement. DV cassette is Tumbleweed Film and Info. MTR audio cassette is Esay (S.A. Griffin).
    - Kei Kunihiro Spoken Vocal, 1997; yrlsc_2248_195_001; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:50:51) (Box 195, Case 1)
      CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are available for access. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
      Transcribed from conatiner: "1) Kerouac Fest Lowell, 2)Boston, 3)San Fernando Valley, 4) Newport Beach La (Recommended)"
    - Swinging in the Shadows Venice West and the LA Scene, 2002; yrlsc_2248_195_002; Kerr, Mary; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:09:20) (Box 195, Case 2)
      Transcribed from container: "Demo"
    - Stuart Z Perkoff Memorial, 1994 June 24; yrlsc_2248_195_003; Long, Philomene, 1940-2007; Raven Productions; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 1:39:11) (Box 195, Case 3)
      Content Note: filmed at Beyond Baroque in Venice, CA. Memorial hosted by Philomeme Long.
    - River Alchemy featuring The L.A. Mudpeople, 2001 August 12; yrlsc_2248_195_004; Solar Video Productions; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:27:30) (Box 195, Case 4)
      Transcribed from container: "Out and About with Roger Martin-Ep #176 WAYS OF THE RIVERS Arts and Environment of the Niger Delta. RIVER ALCHEMY Featuring the L.A. Mudpeople"
    - The Son of Satan and 4 Other Films, undated; yrlsc_2248_195_005; Villard, JJ; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:24:43) (Box 195, Case 5)
      Transcribed from container: "To Linda B, From JJV [includes JJ Villard's address, phone number, and email] jjvillard@hotmail.com, 1716 Santa Barbara St Santa Barbara CA 93101, 805 432 0390. "
    - Undying Love Unending: Jack Micheline, 1998 March 3; yrlsc_2248_195_006; Cloud House Poetry Archives; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 2:03:00) (Box 195, Case 6)
      Content note: Memorial for Jack Micheline
    - Neal Cassady In The Backhouse On The Road, 1990; yrlsc_2248_195_007; Key-Z Productions; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:46:19) (Box 195, Case 7)
      Transcribed from container: "This production contains vintage footage filmed in the proime of the 1960s. You can now listen to Cassady's raps, watchi his moves, and discover for yourself why he was called the fastestmanalive!"
    - Can You Pass The Acid Test, 1990; yrlsc_2248_195_008; Key-Z Productions; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:51:53) (Box 195, Case 8)
      Transcribed from container: "Featuring: the Merry Pranksters, The Grateful Dead, Ken Kesey, Neal Cassady, Wavy Gravy, Owlsy, The Fugs and the Happenings of the Acid Test"
    - The Luxurious Tigers of Obnoxious Agreement, 1997 July 6; yrlsc_2248_195_009; Carma Bums; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 1:28:29) (Box 195, Case 9)
      Transcribed from container: "2nd Version"
    - The Poets, 1995; yrlsc_2248_195_010; Guerilla Filmaker Productions; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 1:47:41) (Box 195, Case 10)
      Content Note: features poets Robert Chambers, Keith Mason, Steve Abee, Luis Rodrigues, Eben Eldridge, Ruben Martinez, Murilene Murphy, Hassan Jamal, S.A. Griffin, and Ellyn Maybe
    - Griffin's Tumbleweed in a Box with Scott Wannberg and Iris Berry, 2002 April 5; yrlsc_2248_195_011; Griffin, S.A., 1954-; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:06:10) (Box 195, Case 11)
    - J.W. McCullough, undated; yrlsc_2248_195_012; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:17:11) (Box 195, Case 12)
    - Act of Kindness, 1993 April 15; yrlsc_2248_196_001; Griffin, S.A., 1954-; Rose of Sharon Productions; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:49:13) (Box 196, Case 1)
    - Griffin's Insensitive Naked Man poem and interview, The Carma Bums, Tribe Must Be President, undated; yrlsc_2248_196_002; Victoria Looseleaf; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:56:16) (Box 196, Case 2)
    - Act of Love, 1993 February 12; yrlsc_2248_196_003; Carma Bums; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:27:03) (Box 196, Case 3)
    - Jack Michelin at Nadeau House (B), 1994 March 13; yrlsc_2248_196_004; 1 video recordings (1 U-matic; Duration: 0:27:18) (Box 196, Case 4)
    - Best of Boss, 1985 October 28; yrlsc_2248_196_005; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 1:02:00) (Box 196, Case 5)
      Transcribed from container: "Fish Karma, Lauren Ann Bogen, Doug Knott, Michael Mollett, Linda Sibio, EZTV, 'Best of Boss;"
    - Jack Michelin at Nadeau House (A), 1994 March 13; yrlsc_2248_196_006; 1 video recordings (1 U-matic; Duration: 32:40:00) (Box 196, Case 6)
    - Best of Boss Volume I, 1985 December 17; yrlsc_2248_196_007; Griffin, S.A., 1954-; Bruner, Michael; 1 video recordings (1 U-matic; Duration: 0:48:46) (Box 196, Case 7)
    - Onword 3/5/1992 to 3/8/1992, 1992 March 5-8; yrlsc_2248_197_001; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:57:00) (Box 197, Case 1)
      Transcribed from container: "Onword 3/5/1992 with Rats with Keys, Eric Brown, Bill Mahoney, Randy Horton; 3/8/1992 with S.F. Folks, Kathi Geores, Domimique Lowell, Bucky Sinister, Alexander Lawrence, John Lange"
    - Onword California with the LA Cacophony Society, undated; yrlsc_2248_197_002; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:02:00) (Box 197, Case 2)
    - Onword Ellyn Maybe and Ron M., 1992 March 24-April 9; yrlsc_2248_197_003; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 2:00:00) (Box 197, Case 3)
      Transcribed from container: "3/24/1992 Ellyn Maybem Blakeslee Stevens, Johnny Speed; 4/9/1992 S.A. Griffin, Grandpa Speed"
    - Onword 3/22/1992 to 3/31/1992, 1992 March 22-31; yrlsc_2248_197_004; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 2:00:00) (Box 197, Case 4)
      Transcribed from container: "Onword 3/19/1992 with Doug Knott, Mike Mollett, Dave, Rafael; 3/31/1992 with Ron Maxson, Vic Day"
    - Onword 2/23/1992 to 3/1/1992, 1992 February 23-March 1; yrlsc_2248_197_005; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:55:00) (Box 197, Case 5)
      Transcribed from container: "Onword 2/23/1992 with Laurel Ann Bogen; 3/1/1992 J.W. McCullough, L.A. Cacophony Society, Blakeslee Stevens, Max Roach"
    - Onword 4/15/1992, 1992 April 15; yrlsc_2248_197_006; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:59:29) (Box 197, Case 6)
      Transcribed from container: "Manazar Gamboa, Naomi, Heather Haley, St. Theresa Stone, Ron Maxson, Johnny Speed"
    - Onword 2/2/1992 to 2/9/1992, 1992 February 2-9; yrlsc_2248_197_007; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:55:00) (Box 197, Case 7)
      Transcribed from container: "Onword 2/2/1992 with Scott Wannberg, Mike Mollett, Doug Knott; 2/16/1992 with Jack Brewer, taped 2/12/1992"
    - The Carma Bums, undated; yrlsc_2248_197_008; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:53:09) (Box 197, Case 8)
    - Phone Story of Carma Bums 1991 Tour of Words, 1991 August 19; yrlsc_2248_197_009; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:02:00) (Box 197, Case 9)
      Transcribed from container: "The movie as told by Skie Bender and Kwin Jacobs, Mike Mollett"
    - The Carma Bums in Albuquerque, undated; yrlsc_2248_197_010; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:31:00) (Box 197, Case 10)
    - More Hal Burns, 1991 August 9; yrlsc_2248_197_011; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:33:00) (Box 197, Case 11)
      Trasncribed from container: "Con. 9A Cards Corn Dog 1 Underrg 9B Sync Audio"
    - KXLU Lost Tribe Show, undated; yrlsc_2248_197_012; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:00:00) (Box 197, Case 12)
    - The Carma Bums/Lost Tribe, undated; yrlsc_2248_197_013; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:21:00) (Box 197, Case 13)
    - Carma Bums Performance Discussion, undated; yrlsc_2248_197_014; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:02:00) (Box 197, Case 14)
      Transcribed from container: "Performance discussion at Lorraine's with C.B.s"
    - Lost Tribe (Opening Song), undated; yrlsc_2248_197_015; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:00:53) (Box 197, Case 15)
      Transcribed from container: "All on side A. B-blank"
    - Lost Tribe (End Song), undated; yrlsc_2248_197_016; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:40:34) (Box 197, Case 16)
    - Morgan and the Lady Chained to the Mast, 1905 June 5; yrlsc_2248_197_017; Griffin, S.A., 1954-; Sargent, Ken; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:12:29) (Box 197, Case 17)
    - Breakout (Everything is Alright), 1985; yrlsc_2248_197_018; Griffin, S.A., 1954-; Sargent, Ken; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:04:45) (Box 197, Case 18)
    - Phone Machine #4, undated; yrlsc_2248_197_019; Griffin, S.A., 1954-; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:15:53) (Box 197, Case 19)
    - Phone Machine #1, 1990-1991; yrlsc_2248_197_020; Griffin, S.A., 1954-; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:48:23) (Box 197, Case 20)
      List of all voice messages with names and dates included on container
    - Phone Machine #2, undated; yrlsc_2248_197_021; Griffin, S.A., 1954-; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:54:46) (Box 197, Case 21)
      Transcribed from insert: "Corny ballads and crazy things on their way to France"
    - Phone Machine #3, undated; yrlsc_2248_197_022; Griffin, S.A., 1954-; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:43:00) (Box 197, Case 22)
    - So If They Ever Name, undated; yrlsc_2248_198_001; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:32:00) (Box 198, Case 1)
      Content note: jazz music and spoken word compilation
    - Past Lives, undated; yrlsc_2248_198_002; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:24:34) (Box 198, Case 2)
    - Tazza Café, undated; yrlsc_2248_198_003; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:39:41) (Box 198, Case 3)
    - Nine Cloud KXLU, undated; yrlsc_2248_198_004; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:32:00) (Box 198, Case 4)
    - Atomic Adagio, undated; yrlsc_2248_198_005; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:11:52) (Box 198, Case 5)
    - Joseph Richard Brewer Shit Gets Heard, 1993; yrlsc_2248_198_006; Brewer, Joseph; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:00:00) (Box 198, Case 6)
      From the Grand Rapids Corporate Territory
    - Waco, undated; yrlsc_2248_198_007; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:27:09) (Box 198, Case 7)
    - Beat America, undated; yrlsc_2248_198_008; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:18:00) (Box 198, Case 8)
      Corso, Henry Miller, Kesey, Cassady, Grateful Dead, Snyder, Ferlinghehi, Kerouac Poems, Burroughs, Ginsberg
    - Montfort Interview #1, 2002 December 6; yrlsc_2248_198_009; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:56:00) (Box 198, Case 9)
      Transcribed from insert: "SA Griffin Interview for Beat Scene Magazine England [content:discuss Linda King and relationship with Bukowski]"
    - Montfort Interview #2, 2002 December 6; yrlsc_2248_198_010; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:23:12) (Box 198, Case 10)
      Transcribed from insert: "SA Griffin Interview for Beat Scene Magazine England"
    - Bukowski Reading, undated; yrlsc_2248_198_011; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:32:16) (Box 198, Case 11)
    - Bukowski Reads His Poetry (Takoma Records 1980), yrlsc_2248_198_012; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:39:40) (Box 198, Case 12)
    - Laurel Ann Bogen The Rat City Variations, 1993-1995; yrlsc_2248_198_013; Bogen, Laurel Ann; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:47:27) (Box 198, Case 13)
    - Duke McVinnie, 1992; yrlsc_2248_198_014; McVinnie, Duke; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:12:00) (Box 198, Case 14)
    - Fuzzy Doodah, 1995; yrlsc_2248_198_015; Beat Not Beat Music; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:16:23) (Box 198, Case 15)
    - Jay Sosnicki 3rd Eye Dropper, 1996; yrlsc_2248_198_016; Jay Sosnicki; Nuthing Sacred; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:22:45) (Box 198, Case 16)
    - Zendik Farm Band (The Loser), 1989; yrlsc_2248_198_017; Zendik Farm Band; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:46:57) (Box 198, Case 17)
    - Hugh Phukovsky Wordcore, undated; yrlsc_2248_198_018; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:24:48) (Box 198, Case 18)
      Transcribed from container: "Ferlinghetti 1978, Kerouac Poems; Burroughs; Ginsberg. Corso; Henry Miller; Kesey; Cassady/Grateful Dead; Snyder"
    - Sachharine Trust (Bass Lines), undated; yrlsc_2248_198_019; Sachharine Trust (Musical Group); 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:06:08) (Box 198, Case 19)
      Transcribed from container: "2 songs"
    - Ellen Maybe A Day in the Life of the Working Poor Xylophone Player, 1991; yrlsc_2248_198_020; Pinsker, Ellyn; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:59:48) (Box 198, Case 20)
      Transcribed from container: "Recorded live at Iguana Café, UCLA, and in artist's room"
    - The Sensitive Side of Jack Brewer, undated; yrlsc_2248_198_021; Brewer, Jack; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:31:00) (Box 198, Case 21)
    - Bobbo Staron My Name Is Trouble, 1989; yrlsc_2248_198_022; Staron, Bobbo; Rose of Sharon Records; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:29:49) (Box 198, Case 22)
    - Bobbo Staron Big Time Demo, 1992; yrlsc_2248_198_023; Staron, Bobbo; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:17:03) (Box 198, Case 23)
    - Yellow Untitled-This Side (Voice Message from Emily), undated; yrlsc_2248_198_024; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:18:27) (Box 198, Case 24)
      Transcribed from container: "This Side"
    - Ken Tao's Alchemical Orchestra Just Lack Charisma, 1994; yrlsc_2248_198_025; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:01:00) (Box 198, Case 25)
      Transcribed from container: "Fall 1994"
    - Laurel Ann Bogen Do Iguanas Dance Under the Moonlight, 1984; yrlsc_2248_198_026; Bogen, Laurel Ann; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:40:53) (Box 198, Case 26)
      Transcribed from container: "Recorded live at Al's Bar"
    - Scott Wannberg 1991, yrlsc_2248_199_001; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:25:00) (Box 199, Case 1)
    - Scott Wannberg #2, 1991 June 24; yrlsc_2248_199_002; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:19:00) (Box 199, Case 2)
    - Scott Wannberg #3, undated; yrlsc_2248_199_003; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 2:03:00) (Box 199, Case 3)
    - Scott Wannberg 08/1994, 1994 August 1; yrlsc_2248_199_004; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:33:00) (Box 199, Case 4)
    - Scott Wannberg, 1995 May 27; yrlsc_2248_199_005; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:02:00) (Box 199, Case 5)
    - Scott Wannberg 07/24/1996, 1996 July 24; yrlsc_2248_199_006; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:21:21) (Box 199, Case 6)
    - Scott Wannberg 10/1994, 1994 October 1; yrlsc_2248_199_007; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:31:26) (Box 199, Case 7)
    - Stuart Z Perkoff / James Ryan Morris, undated; yrlsc_2248_199_008; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:33:00) (Box 199, Case 8)
    - Mike Bruner 1984, yrlsc_2248_199_009; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:13:27) (Box 199, Case 9)
    - Mike Mollett Mudpeople Interview, 1993 July 1; yrlsc_2248_199_010; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:19:00) (Box 199, Case 10)
    - Bob Branaman, 1999 December 6; yrlsc_2248_199_011; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:34:00) (Box 199, Case 11)
      Content note: Interview for magazine with SA Griffin about Branaman's work. Transcribed from container: "Sweet Lorraine"
    - Jack Micheline 1982, yrlsc_2248_199_012; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:45:28) (Box 199, Case 12)
    - Jack Micheline MVD Boulder, 1983; yrlsc_2248_199_013; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:47:51) (Box 199, Case 13)
    - Blakeslee Stevens American Hotel/Humanesque, 1985-1986; yrlsc_2248_199_014; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:58:20) (Box 199, Case 14)
    - Lon Spiegelman Mail Art Interview, undated; yrlsc_2248_199_015; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:00:00) (Box 199, Case 15)
      Content note: interview about international mail art movment, culture, and private archives
    - Sebastin Cabot and Other Stuff/William Burroughs, undated; yrlsc_2248_199_016; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:31:00) (Box 199, Case 16)
    - Fred Neil Live, 1980 June 1; yrlsc_2248_199_017; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:58:12) (Box 199, Case 17)
      Transcrbied from container: "Fred Neil/Tony Scibella "Prettiest Train" "The Kid in America" at Café Nepenthes [Side 2] "The Kid in America" continued Live at the Elephant"
    - Mike Meloan, undated; yrlsc_2248_199_018; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:59:55) (Box 199, Case 18)
      Content note: Meloan and Frank On Buk, Et Al
    - Diane DiPrima Interview with Marie Kazalia, 2002 April 4; yrlsc_2248_199_019; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:13:00) (Box 199, Case 19)
    - Neal Cassady, undated; yrlsc_2248_199_020; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:23:00) (Box 199, Case 20)
    - Jack Brewer, undated; yrlsc_2248_199_021; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:33:00) (Box 199, Case 21)
      Transcribed from container: "Jack Brewer poetry master copy. Jack Brewer Poetry tape + Standup"
    - Williams Carlos Williams/Saccharine Trust, undated; yrlsc_2248_199_022; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 1:18:00) (Box 199, Case 22)
      Content Note: Last 4 minutes of side A and most of side B include live recording of Saccharine Trust concert. The recording is mostly the band talking before and in between songs rather than recordings of the actual songs, introduced as the "first Saccharine Trust bootleg". At 01:20:00 music program recorded off KXLU, poor quality with distortion and crackle with gain change in the middle
    - Jack Kerouac on Beat Generation, undated; yrlsc_2248_199_023; 1 sound recordings (1 audiocassette; Duration: 0:58:53) (Box 199, Case 23)
    - onTarget Live at the Grassy Knoll tape 2, undated; yrlsc_2248_203_001; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 0:10:48) (Box 203, Case 1)
      Content note: features a poetry reading by S.A. Griffin
    - Cabaret X, 2002; yrlsc_2248_203_002; Franchot, Pascal; Stevens, Steve; 1 video recordings (1 VHS; Duration: 1:18:19) (Box 203, Case 2)